[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This color is the national color of the Netherlands. In Canada and the United States it is associated with the field of engineering.", "correct_answer": "Orange", "incorrect_answers": ["Purple", "Black", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous 19th century nurse gained the moniker Lady with the lamp during the Crimean War?", "correct_answer": "Florence Nightingale", "incorrect_answers": ["Molly Pitcher", "Carrie Nation", "Mary Mallon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the worlds smallest independent state with a population in 2007 of approximately 821.", "correct_answer": "Vatican City", "incorrect_answers": ["Monaco", "San Marino", "Tuvalu"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Natale Cole is the daughter of Nat King Cole. Who was her famous grandfather?", "correct_answer": "Duke Ellington", "incorrect_answers": ["Count Basie", "Terry Coles", "Roger Coles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Hollywood actor and singer performed the song Singin in the Rain in the 1952 musical film Singin in the Rain?", "correct_answer": "Gene Kelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Frank Sinatra", "Fred Astaire", "Dean Martin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What day did Rocky choose to fight Drago in Rocky IV?", "correct_answer": "Christmas Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Thanksgiving", "Good Friday", "New Years Day"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was director Christopher Nolans first choice for the role of Leonard Shelby in the movie Memento?", "correct_answer": "Brad Pitt", "incorrect_answers": ["Joe Pantoliano", "Johnny Depp", "Stephen Baldwin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Denzel Washington has a son who signed to play with the New Orleans Saints.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This kind of beer, produced from wild yeast through a process called spontaneous fermentation, has a distinctive, cidery flavour with slightly sour aftertaste.", "correct_answer": "lambic beer", "incorrect_answers": ["cantillon beer", "boon beer", "chapeau beer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What unripened fruit is used for the preparation of the spicy Thai salad Som tam?", "correct_answer": "Papaya", "incorrect_answers": ["Banana", "Mango", "Lychee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Blackjack, what does a \u201cnatural\u201d hand consist of?", "correct_answer": "Ace and a ten-valued card", "incorrect_answers": ["Two equal cards", "Two even-numbered card", "Ace and a Jack"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following medications is for enuresis (bed-wetting)?", "correct_answer": "DDAVP (Arginine Vasopressin)", "incorrect_answers": ["Senokot (senna)", "Sansert (methysergide)", "THC (tetrahydrocannabinol)"]}]